Zhang Tianyou.
Now even Heaven is on my side.
How can you possibly fight me?
Move!
Let me go!
Let go!
Jiushuang.
Miss Sheng.
You two,
would you rather die with Zhang Tianyou,
or live happily with me, Li Xiao?
Then I'd rather die!
Good.
How devoted.
Miss Sheng,
what about you?
Ling Yu.
At least you know what's good for you.
Don't worry, I won't mistreat you.
Smells so good.
Use explosives to cave this whole place in.
Even if this filthy dirt-digger survives the cave-in,
he'll still be like a rat,
digging his way out for the next decade.
Look.
Look at this pathetic, dejected face,
looking like his whole family just died.
Zhang Tianyou.
Look at you now.
This feels great!
Let's go.
Zhang Tianyou!
Zhang Tianyou, pull yourself together!
The Zhang Tianyou I know wouldn't act like this.
Come with me.
Young Master Qi, that's enough.
Just leave him in one piece. Times are tough for everyone.
Cooled off? We're done here.
Let's go.
Young Master!
That bastard Li Xiao blew up the path!
Is this place gonna collapse?!
Southeast corner, stick to the wall!
Go!
Go, go, go, go!
Rat Bro!
Are you still in one piece?
I'm fine.
Look,
Young Master, make yourself useful.
Light this torch.
I'll go scout ahead.
Zhang Tianyou, you...
do you think I suddenly snapped out of it?
I was just putting on an act for Li Xiao.
You have to let him get cocky before he goes crazy.
Hope I didn't scare you half to death.
I was just wondering...
how Ling Yu is doing.
Ling Yu?
When she left with Li Xiao earlier,
we exchanged a look.
I signaled her to look for a chance out there
to see if she could get us out.
What's wrong, Rat Bro?
It's no use.
It's completely blocked front and back.
We're just waiting to die.
Chun'er!
Stop shouting.
I gave her a double dose of Worry-Free Powder.
She's probably sleeping so deeply she forgot her name.
Uncle Mei and Brother Wan are here.
Let's go.
I'll take you to meet them.
Remember our script?
You only have one line.
Everything Brother Li Xiao said is true.
If you get it wrong,
next time it won't be just one person lying here.
Let's go.
Brother Wan.
I brought Ling Yu back safely.
Thank heavens!
Where is my sister?
Is she still alive?
Chun'er!
It's all my fault for being useless.
I failed to protect Chun'er.
To save us in the secret chamber, Chun'er
was attacked by Zhang Tianyou's Two-Headed Venomous Snake
and got bitten.
She was infected with a strange poison
and is still unconscious.
And Jiushuang...
Jiushuang!
That bastard pushed her into the Pit of Ten Thousand Snakes.
Not even her bones remain.
Two-headed snakes? The Pit of Ten Thousand Snakes?
Li Xiao,
where exactly did you go?
It was terrifying!
The structure inside was extremely complex,
with a diverse ecosystem.
My brothers and I fought a bloody battle
just to make it out alive.
If I, Li Xiao, am lying at all,
may lightning strike me down!
Ling Yu,
tell Brother Wan if that's true.
That's right.
Everything Brother Li Xiao said is true.
Well, over there,
there were indeed a lot of small animals.
Where is the item?
Don't tell me it was also bitten by some two-headed snake.
The item is here.
Go get it.
The item is fine.
Brother Wan, it's completely intact.
Although it was a narrow escape,
but fortunately, I didn't let anyone down.
Since you're so capable,
when the head of the Mei family returns,
I'll propose you become the Acting Leader.
Me?
How could I possibly accept that?
I will serve until my dying breath!
Don't be in such a hurry to die.
Finding the Zhang family descendant is what matters now.
Do you have a lead on this?
Don't worry, Brother Wan.
I've got it all in the palm of my hand.
They won't get away.
Go.
Find someone immediately.
Yes.
Li Xiao.
What exactly happened?
Uncle Mei,
I'm so sorry!
I was useless.
I couldn't bring Jiushuang out.
It's all my fault!
Here.
Press on this.
Young Master,
if you have any secret tricks up your sleeve,
just use them!
Don't hide them anymore.
I don't want to die here.
Look at what I'm wearing!
The magnetic field here is chaotic,
yin energy is leaking,
and yin and yang are unbalanced.
If my deduction is correct,
the next Geomantic Tide is in four days max.
The chamber's structure will be at its weakest.
If we manage to survive until then,
we might still have a fighting chance.
Actually, there's another way.
I just hope we won't have to use it.
Zhang Tianyou,
can you tell me now?
Alright.
Back then...
when exploring the Tidal Tomb together,
Wan, Mei, Qi, and Sheng
were merely servants of the Zhang Family.
But I don't know
what exactly happened in that Tidal Tomb.
After coming out,
each had the Zhang Family's Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye.
They suddenly transformed
into today's Four Great Families.
Thus provoking the tomb's evil entities,
resulting in 20 years of constant disasters.
So you sought to gather the Talisman, Curse, Seal, and Eye
to become the leader of the four families,
just to uncover the truth of what happened back then.
Only by returning to where it all began
can we learn what happened in the Tidal Tomb
and what the Dragon-Seeking Zhang Family experienced 20 years ago.
And also take back everything belonging to the Zhang Family.
I also want to know,
within The Four Great Families,
what the root cause of the bizarre deaths really is.
So it really is you,
Zhang Tianyou.
What's that sound?
Someone's here.
It's not human.
It's an anomaly.